Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Maps and Atlases of Boston, 1874 -- 1928; MS102.004; 99 Digital Object(s)
  - 1928 Atlas, MS102.004.003; 38 Digital Object(s)
    - Plate 33. Part of Wards 5 and 21, 1928; MS102.004.003.DO.00033; G.W. Bromley & Co.
      Part of Wards 5 and 21 included in G. W. Bromley & Co.'s 1928 Atlas of the city of Boston. Boston Proper and Back Bay from actual surveys and official plans. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Plate 34. Part of Wards 5 and 21., 1928; MS102.004.003.DO.00034; G.W. Bromley & Co.
    - Plate 35. Part of Wards 5 and 21., 1928; MS102.004.003.DO.00035; G.W. Bromley & Co.
    - Plate 36. Part of Wards 4, 5 and 21., 1928; MS102.004.003.DO.00036; G.W. Bromley & Co.
      Part of Wards 4, 5 and 21.included in G. W. Bromley & Co.'s 1928 Atlas of the city of Boston. Boston Proper and Back Bay from actual surveys and official plans. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Map index., 1928; MS102.004.003.DO.00037; G.W. Bromley & Co.
      Map index included in G. W. Bromley & Co.'s 1928 Atlas of the city of Boston. Boston Proper and Back Bay from actual surveys and official plans. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Title Page and street index., 1928; MS102.004.003.DO.00038; G.W. Bromley & Co.
      Title page and street index included in G. W. Bromley & Co.'s 1928 Atlas of the city of Boston. Boston Proper and Back Bay from actual surveys and official plans. Institute of Museum and Library Services